how do you to show your face around here
Jessie well I know how much you miss me
I still have a picture of me at the
hideout I hear that you look at it every
day
flattering really how do you even live
just as sanghun ash how about we let
bygones be bygones
I was hoping you'd make an exception for
old times sake
you know you never were might I bash too
competent to rich me always were the
ambitious one ash you make that sound
like a bad thing you'd still be on a
farm if it weren't for me
yet some days it doesn't sound so bad my
business
mouths Mars he's just fun thank you for
your concern
mom nice bikes gah - what'd you do with
it Jessie parked it somewhere I'm damned
if I remember where I left the keys
though
remind me to stay off your backside
there's only one way you get to leave
the gang bad guys always gonna be this
way oh now who's the better shot